

Mamatha Mereddy

Get in touch!

Mobile:

42799884

Email

mamathavangala1@gmail.com

Linkedin:

rhttps://www.linkedin.com/in/mereddy-mamatha/

Github:

https://github.com/mamathamereddy

Adress:

Kirkebjerg Alle 97 st.th, 2605 Brøndby

Skills:

Html₅

css3

Javascript(ES6)

Node.js /Express

MySQl/MongoDB

React

ReactNative

GitBash GitHub

Languages Spoken

European:

Danish

Asian:

Telugu, Hindhi

Other:

English

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

- -RailsGirls-Copenhagen (2019 -Present) Building Mentee-mentor platform using React as Front-end and ruby as Back-end

Frontend developer

Enthusiastic and highly motivated with hands-on experience in creating websites that provide a clean and user-friendly experience. Also, I am highly motivated to learn new technologies in a fast pace, and deepen my knowledge and experience in coding and development

Work EXperience

Frontend Developer(intern)

RateDateMate Aps

06/2020 - Present,

Tolker

Tolk Denmark

2018 - 2020,

Production Specialist

DFD A/s

2011 - 2017,

Projects

Weather App - Display weather detail's based on user input https://mamathamereddy.github.io/weather-app/

MealSharing App- https://hyf-meals-sharing.herokuapp.com/

GitHub User Search - searching github users based on the what you type in the input.

https://react-github-user-search-app.herokuapp.com/

EDUCATION

FullStack Development

HackYour Future

09/2019 - 04/2020, Copehhaegn, Denmark

Web developer course is educating in the following languages and Hands-on experience using HTML5, CSS, Javascript, NodeJS, Database(My SQL), ExpressJs, React.

During my final project at
HackYourFuture, I worked with a a
team of 13 members on
developing a web app for showing
batch details in vertical farming for
the company called SEASONY
Using above technologies as well
as Firebase, Knex, Swagger,
Storybook among others .Project
can find on:: https://fpclass11.herokuapp.com/

-Master's in Computer Application, Osmania University-India 2004 - 2007,

-Bachlor's in Computer Science Osmania University

2001 - 2004,